Poland Subject Files, Inclusive: 1947-2002, undated, Bulk: 1960-1989
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- General Subject Files, 1947-2001, undated; 1
  - Atheism. General, 1961-1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Atheist Work. Secularization, 1961-1986, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Confrontations Between Solidarity and Polish Government, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Party Response to 1981 Confrontations, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Party Response to 1981 Confrontations: "Extraordinary" Congress (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Individual Communists and Ideologists, 1964-1965, 1977, 1981-1983,1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Individual Communists and Ideologists. Gierek, Edward, 1976, 1978, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Individual Communists and Ideologists. Jaruzelski, Wojchiech, 1981-1989, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Individual Communists and Ideologists. Kania, Stanislaw, 1981, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Ideological Propaganda. Education. Work, 1974-1980, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Ethics and Morality, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture. Economy. Labor, 1962, 1965, 1974-1975, 1981, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture, 1963, 1974-1976, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Economy, 1976-1989, 2000, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Economy. Debt Crisis, 1977-1990 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Economy. Poland and Comecon Countries, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Economic Reforms and Price Increases, 1974-1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Consumer Shortages, 1976 - 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Dissidents on Economy, 1980-1981, 1988, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Polish Economy Under Martial Law, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - International Contracts and Trade, 1965, 1974-1978, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Labor, 1973, 1977, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Education. Science. Geography, 1968, 1971-1988, 1990, 1992, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Solidarity on Educational Reform, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Ecology, 1986 - 1990, 1993, 1995, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Health. Leisure. Sport. Tourism, 1979-1986, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - General Info for Visitors to Poland, 1971, 1974-1980, 1985, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Psychology (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Information Services, 1972, 1976 - 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Solidarity in Mass Media, 1972-1973, 1981 - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Individual Writers. Miłosz, Czesław, 1980-1982, 1984, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Culture, 1963-1965, 1974-1975, 1980-1983, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Culture. Film and Performance, 1962-1968, 1971-1989, 1993, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Culture. Literature, 1956, 1965-1999 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Culture. Art and Music, 1964-1979, 1987- 1995, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Women, 1981, 1985, 1989 - 1994, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Children and Youth, 1962, 1968, 1973-1989, 1993, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Society. Family. Everyday life, 1964-1966, 1971-1981, 1986, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Social Problems and Morality, 1969-1970, 1977-1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Drug and Alcohol Consumption, 1971-1987, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Family Planning and Abortion, 1971, 1980-1989, 1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Political Corruption, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Family Life, 1964, 1972-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Visual Materials, 1980, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Internees and Internment Camps, 1981 - 1988, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Emigration, 1981 - 1989, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Immigration to Poland, 1984 - 1986, 1989 - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - International Relations. The West and the World, 1981, 1984 - 1987, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - International Relations. The West and the World. Economic Sanctions, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - State Visits, 1982 - 1999 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - State Visits. Margaret Thatcher, 1987 - 1989, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - State Visits. George Bush, 1987 - 1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - State Visits. Helmut Kohl, 1989 - 1990, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Auschwitz. History and Development, 1983, 1985, 1989 - 2000 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Auschwitz. Carmelite Convent Controversy, 1988 - 1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Auschwitz. Cross controversy, 1989, 1995 -1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - KOR. Trial, 1981, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Individual Dissidents. Walesa, Lech, 1982 - 1995, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Solidarity. Poems, Songs, and Prayers, 1982, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Church-State Relations, 1984 - 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Religious Life in Poland, 1984, 1988 - 1994, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Church Relations to Solidarity and Other Dissident Groups, 1982 - 1984, 1988 - 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Holocaust, 1983 - 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Denominational Subject Files, 1954-2002, undated; 2
  This series includes information on the Roman Catholic Church, Judaism, and Anti-Semitism following World War II. The Roman Catholic files are the most extensive and contain information from general history of the church to detailed information on particular members of the clergy, including Pope John Paul II, Cardinal Josef Glemp, Fr. Stanislaw Malkowski, Fr. Jerzy Popieluszko, and others.
  - Seventh Day Adventist Church, 1970-1987, 1999, 2000, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Anglican Church, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Armenian Church, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Church. General (1 of 3), 1971-1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Church. General (2 of 3), 1982-1999, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Church. General (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Church Life, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Baptist Church. Opening New Churches, 1981-1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Church. Clergy and Priesthood, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Church. Relations with Fellow Believers and Other Denominations, 1978-1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Baptist Church. Statistics, 1970-1988, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Buddhism, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Church of Christ, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Islam, 1970-1993, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1955-1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Judaism. General, 1970-1989, 1994-1999, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Judaism. History. Auschwitz, 1990-1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Judaism. History. Culture, 1966-2002, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Judaism. Bibliography. Book Reviews, 1966-1988, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Judaism. Jewish Ghetto. Warsaw. Lodz, 1963-1988, 1995, 1998, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Judaism. Anti-Semitism (1 of 2), 1968-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Judaism. Anti-Semitism (2 of 2), 1966-2000, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Judaism. Jewish-Catholic Relations, 1978-1999, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Judaism. Polish-Jewish Relations, 1966-2001 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Crimes against Polish Jews, 1973-2001 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Persecution. Individual Cases, 1967-1978 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Karaitic Religious Union, 1980-1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Lutheran Church. History. Culture, 1969-1987, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Lutheran Church. Administration, 1978-1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lutheran Church. Administration, 1977-1988, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lutheran Clergy. Priesthood, 1975-2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Lutheran Church. Statistics, 1969-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lutheran Church. Relations with Fellow Believers, 1980-2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Lutheran Church. Relations with Roman Catholic Church, 1979-1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Lutheran Church. Involvement in Secular Affairs, 1980-1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Methodist Church, 1969-1988, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Church of the Latter-Day Saints (Mormon), 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Old Catholic Church/Polish Catholic Church, 1965-1988 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Old-Rite Church, 1972-1988, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Orthodox Church (1 of 2), 1959-1981 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Orthodox Church (2 of 2), 1982-1990, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Orthodox Church. Clergy. Priesthood, 1980-1985 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Orthodox Church. Statistics, 1975-1986 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Protestant Churches (1 of 2), 1937-1944 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Protestant Churches (2 of 2), 1970-1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Reformed Church, 1968-1988, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - The Christian Science Association (The Church of Christ, Scientist), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Roman Catholic Church. General (1 of 2), 1958-2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. General (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. History. General (1 of 3), 1972-1988, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. History. General (2 of 3), undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. History. General (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. History. Post-War Period (1 of 3), 1954-2000, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church. History. Post-War Period (2 of 3), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church. History. Post-War Period (3 of 3), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Individual Roman Catholics, 1981-1983, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Bartoszewski, Wladyslaw, 1970-1982, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Bender, Ryszard, 1979 February (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Cywinski, Bohdan, 1979-1980, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Kisielewski, Stefan, 1975-1981, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Mazowiecki, Tadeusz, 1967-1983 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Ozdowski, Jerzy, 1980-1981, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Piasecki, Boleslaw, 1965-1978, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Reiff, Ryszard, 1981, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Switon, Kazimierz, 1978-1983, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Turowicz, Jerzy, 1976-1999, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Wozniakowski, Jacek, 1978-1981 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Individual Roman Catholics. Zawieyski, Jerzy, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Roman Catholic Church Administration, 1970-1986, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. State. Law (1 of 2), 1965-1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. State. Law (2 of 2), 1966-1986, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (1 of 11), 1955-1966 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (2 of 11), 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (3 of 11), 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (4 of 11), 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (5 of 11), 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (6 of 11), 1981 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (7 of 11), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (8 of 11), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (9 of 11), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (10 of 11), 1985-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice (11 of 11), undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church-State Relations. Theory and Practice. Crucifixes, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Government Pronouncements on Roman Catholic Church, 1964-1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Government Pronouncements on Roman Catholic Church, 1983-1984, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church's Comments on Government Pronouncements, 1964-1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Opening of New Roman Catholic Churches (1 of 3), 1961-1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Opening of New Roman Catholic Churches (2 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Opening of New Roman Catholic Churches (3 of 3), 1982-1988, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Destruction of Roman Catholic Churches, 1974-1980, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Access to Media, 1971-1983, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Toward Roman Catholic Believers (1 of 2), 1954-1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Toward Roman Catholic Believers (2 of 2), 1980-1996, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. General, 1971-1999, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Marian Cult (1 of 2), 1966-1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Marian Cult (2 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Festivals and Anniversaries, 1975-1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Festivals and Anniversaries. Corpus Christi, 1965-1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Festivals and Anniversaries. Millennium Celebration (1 of 4), 1966 January-March (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Festivals and Anniversaries. Millennium Celebration (2 of 4), 1966 April-June (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Festivals and Anniversaries (3 of 4), 1966 July-December (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Festivals and Anniversaries. Millennium Celebration (4 of 4), 1966-1977, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Saints, 1971-1987, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Saints. St. Kazimierz, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Saints. Fr. Maximilian Kolbe, 1971-1995, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Saints. St. Stanislaus Kostka, 1972-1982, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Saints. Sr. Faustina Kowalska, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Pilgrimages. Holy Places, 1965-1988, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Pilgrimages. Holy Places. Czestochowa (1 of 2), 1962-1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church Life. Pilgrimages. Holy Places. Czestochowa (2 of 2), 1978-1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Press (1 of 3), 1968-1979 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Press (2 of 3), 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Press (3 of 3), 1983-1993, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Religious revival, 1968-1983, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Religious revival. St. Barbara Cult, 1980-1981, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Desecularization Process. Catholic Left, 1967-1987, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Monasticism, 1961-1989, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Priesthood. General, 1973-1999 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Priesthood. Hierarchy, 1961-1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Priesthood. Ordination. Election. Retirement. Deaths., 1961-1989, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (1 of 8), 1968-1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (2 of 8), 1978 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (3 of 8), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (4 of 8), 1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (5 of 8), 1981 January-June (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (6 of 8), 1981 August-December (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (7 of 8), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Plenary Conferences of the Polish Episcopate (8 of 8), 1983-1988, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests., 1980-1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Blachniki, Fr. Frantiszek, 1982-1987, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Hejmo, Fr. Konrad Stanislaw, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Jankowski, Fr. Henryk, 1983-1997, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Kowalczyk, Fr. Stanislaw, 1983 May (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Lewek, Fr. Antoni, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Novak, Fr. Meczyslaw, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Popieluszko, Fr. Jerzy (1 of 6), 1983-1984 October (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Popieluszko, Fr. Jerzy (2 of 6), 1984 November-December (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Popieluszko, Fr. Jerzy (3 of 6), 1985 January (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Popieluszko, Fr. Jerzy (4 of 6), 1985 February (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Popieluszko, Fr. Jerzy (5 of 6), 1985 April-2000, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Popieluszko, Fr. Jerzy (6 of 6), 1983-1984, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Salij, Fr. Jacek, 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Tischner, Fr. Josef, 1981-1989, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Zaliski, Fr. Tadeusz, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Zych, Fr. Sylwester, 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Zieja, Fr. Jan, 1975-1991, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Malkowski, Fr. Stanislaw (1 of 4), 1976-1981 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Malkowski, Fr. Stanislaw (2 of 4), 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Malkowski, Fr. Stanislaw (3 of 4), 1984-1986, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Priests. Malkowski, Fr. Stanislaw (4 of 4), 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops, 1979-1984, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Ablewicz, Jerzi, 1980-1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Barela, Stefan, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Bednoz, Herbert, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Bogdan, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Czacki, Wlodzimierz, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (1 of 10), 1979-1982 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (2 of 10), 1983-1995, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (3 of 10), 1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (4 of 10), 1981 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (5 of 10), 1982 January-June (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (6 of 10), 1982 July-December (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (7 of 10), 1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (8 of 10), 1984 January-May (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (9 of 10), 1984 May-July (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Glemp, Jozef (10 of 10), 1987-1988, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Gublinowicz, Henryk, 1981-1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Hlonda, August, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Kaczmarek, Lech, 1980-1983 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Macharski, Franticzek, 1979-1985, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Majdanski, Kazimierz, 1981-1984 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Materski, Edward, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Mazur, Jan, 1981-1984 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Misiolek, Wladyslaw, 1979-1881 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Moszelewski, Jerzi, 1981-1984 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Nossol, Alfons, 1981-1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Pluta, Wilhelm, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Rechowicz, Marion, 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Rozwadowski, Josef, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Sikorski, Bogdan, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Stroba, Jerzy, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Szymecki, Stanislaw, 1981-1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Tokarczuk, Ignacy, 1979-1983, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan, 1961-1976 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan, 1977-1979 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan, 1982-2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan. Sermons. Pastoral Letters, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan. Sermons. Pastoral Letters, 1981 January-February (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Wyszynski, Stefan. Sermons. Pastoral Letters, 1981 March-1983, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Bishops. Zareba, Jan, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1979 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1984 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla), 1985-1999, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 2-10 June 1979, 1978 October-1979 May (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 2-10 June 1979, 1979 June 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 2-10 June 1979, 1979 June 6-10 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 2-10 June 1979, 1979 June 11-15 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 2-10 June 1979, 1979 June 16-30 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 2-10 June 1979, 1979 July, November, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)